A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A92), 1983-1989; 1.18; 42.93 Cubic Feet; 97 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-97) 1 half letter size document storage box (Box 98)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 85032 A116 - Wilson, Melvin N., 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 186)
      Project title: "A Social Interaction Analysis of Two- and Three-Generational Black Families"
    - RF 85032 A117 - Wei, William, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 187)
      Project title: "Yellow Pearl: A Social History of the Asian American Movement"
    - RF 85032 A114 - Malson, Michelene R., 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 188)
      Project title: "The Strengths of Black Single Parent Families: Identifying Coping Strategies for Self Reliance"
    - RF 85032 A118 - Cortes, Carlos E., 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 189)
      Project title: "The History of Ethnicity and Foreigners in American Feature Films"
    - RF 85037 - Global Committee of Parliamentarians on Population and Development - Publication and Communication Program, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 190-191, Box 30, Folder 192-193)
    - RF 85039 - American Council of Learned Societies - Scholarly Communication and Technology Office, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 194-195)
    - RF 85039 - American Council of Learned Societies - Scholarly Communication and Technology Office: Supplementary Material (Box 31, Folder 196)
    - RF 85043 - University of Pennsylvania - Geographic Medicine Program, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 197-198)
    - RF 85044 - Harvard University - Geographic Medicine Center for Virology and Pediatrics, 1985-1989 (Box 31, Folder 199)
      Grantee changed on October 23, 1985, from Children's Hospital to Harvard University
    - RF 85046 A7 - Bangladesh Fertility Research Programme - Family Planning, 1986, 1988, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 200)
    - RF 85046 A11 - Mahidol University - Family Planning Services in Thailand, 1985-1989 (Box 31, Folder 201, Box 32, Folder 202-203)
    - RF 85046 A12 - Population Council, Inc. - Evaluation of Family Planning Services in Thailand, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 204)
    - RF 85047 A1 - University of Nairobi - Medical Journal Subscriptions, 1985-1986, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 205)
    - RF 85047 A2 - Kamuzora, C. L. (Chrysanth Lwechungura), 1985-1989, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 206-208, Box 33, Folder 209)
      Project title: "High Fertility and Women's Life Circumstances in Peasant Economies: Tanzania"; Research report title: "Women, Changing Value of Children and the Beginning of Fertility Limitation in Africa"
    - RF 85047 A3 - University of Zimbabwe - Child Malnutrition, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 210)
    - RF 85047 A7 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - African Demography, 1986-1990 (Box 33, Folder 211-213)
    - RF 85047 A7 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - African Demography: Supplementary Material (Box 33, Folder 214, Box 34, Folder 215-216)
    - RF 85047 A8 - University of Benin, Nigeria - Effects of Population Growth on the Provision of Social Services, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 217-218)
    - RF 85047 A11 - Sociocultural Determinants of Fertility in Africa - Conference, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 219-220)
    - RF 85049 A22 - Zhejiang Academy of Medicine - Projects in Reproductive Biology, 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 221)
    - RF 85049 A26 - Mahidol University - Microcomputer and Software for Institute for Population and Social Research, 1986-1988 (Box 35, Folder 222)
    - RF 85049 A28 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Research on Antisperm Antibodies and Human Sperm Membrane Proteins, 1984-1990, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 223-224)
    - RF 85050 A221 Lesthaeghe, R. J. (Ronny Jean Leopold), 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 225)
      Project title: "Nuptiality Systems, Social Organization and Demographic Transition in Sub-Saharan Africa"
    - RF 85050 A223 - Duben, Alan, 1985-1988, 1990-1992 (Box 36, Folder 226)
      Project title: "Fertility, Family, and Society in Istanbul, 1880-1940"
    - RF 85050 A225 - Columbia University - Crandon, Mary Elizabeth (Libbet), 1985-1988, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 227-228)
      Project title: "Gender, Work and Fertility: The Social, Economic and Political Impacts of Women's Business Ownership in the Formal Economic Sector in Latin America"
    - RF 85050 A225 - Columbia University - Crandon, Mary Elizabeth (Libbet): Supplementary Material (Box 36, Folder 229)
    - RF 85050 A228 - Oppong, Christine, 1985-1988, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 230-231)
      Monograph title: "Relationships Between Women's Work and Demographic Behaviour: Some Research Evidence in West Africa"
    - RF 85050 A230 - Okojie, Christiana E. E., 1983-1989, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 232-234, Box 38, Folder 235-238)
      Project title: "Women's Status and Fertility in Bendel State: A Comparative Study of Selected Communities"
    - RF 85050 A231 - University of Southern California - India Television and Family Planning, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 239, Box 39, Folder 240-242)
      Project title: "Effects of 'Hum Log', a Television Soap Opera, on Women's Status and Fertility in India"
    - RF 85050 A231 - University of Southern California - India Television and Family Planning: Supplementary Material (Box 39, Folder 243)
    - RF 85050 A231 - University of Southern California - India Television and Family Planning: Supplementary Material: "Effects of 'Hum Log', a Television Soap Opera on the Status of Women and Fertility in India", U-matic; 7 minutes (Box 3, Tape AV 12114)
      Part of grant proposal titled: "Effects of 'Hum Log', a Television Soap Opera on the Status of Women and Fertility in India" - Excerpts from "Hum Log" and "Rajani", two of the pro-development soap operas on Indian television; Submitted by Dr. Everett M. Rogers, Annenberg School of Communications, University of Southern California
    - RF 85050 A235 - Academia Sinica, Taiwan - Fertility and Status of Women in Two Chinese Communities, 1985-1988, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 244)
    - RF 85050 A236 - Pitt, Mark M. and Rosenzweig, Mark R., 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 245)
      Project title: "Fertility, Child Health and Gender Inequality in the Household Allocation of Time"
    - RF 85055 - University of California, San Diego - Center for U.S.-Mexican Studies, 1981-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 246, Box 40, Folder 247-248)
    - RF 85055 - University of California, San Diego - Center for U.S.-Mexican Studies: Supplementary Material (Box 40, Folder 249-250, Box 41, Folder 251-254, Box 42, Folder 255-258, Box 43, Folder 259-262)
    - RF 85056 - Instituto Latinoamericano de Estudios Transnacionales - U.S.-Mexican Relations, 1985-1989 (Box 44, Folder 263-264)
    - RF 85057- (The) Brookings Institution - Impediments to European Economic Growth, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Box 265-267)
    - RF 85057- (The) Brookings Institution - Impediments to European Economic Growth: Supplementary Material (Box 45, Folder 268)
    - RF 85028 A28 - Kyoto Prefectural University- Rice Genetics, 1984-1990 (Box 45, Folder 269)
    - RF 85058 A34 - Disease Resistance in Rice - Workshop, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 270-271)
    - RF 85064 A5 - Bia, Johnson, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 272)
      Fellowship cancelled, February 1, 1987
      Administered by the RF and Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center) (CIMMYT)
    - RF 85064 A5 - Bia, Johnson, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 272A)
    - RF 85064 A7 - Kaimowitz, David, 1985-1990, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 273-276)
      Project title: "Research Study on the Linkages Between Agricultural Research and Technology Transfer", jointly administered by RF and International Service for National Agricultural Research (ISNAR), Netherlands
    - RF 85064 A7 - Kaimowitz, David, 1985-1990, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 273A)
    - RF 85064 A8 - Hopkins, Jane Chadwick, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 277-278)
    - RF 85064 A8 - Hopkins, Jane Chadwick, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 277A)
    - RF 85067 A20 - Social Science Association of Thailand - "Buddhist Approaches to Development" by Dr. Somboon Suksamran, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 279)
    - RF 85067 A21 - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies, Singapore - Publication of "Reflections on Southeast Asian Development", 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 280)
    - RF 85067 A23 - Ake, Claude, 1986-1989, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 281)
      Project title: "Social Transformation in Africa: A Materialist Theory"
    - RF 85067 A24 - Serpell, Robert, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 282)
      Project title: "The Psychological Significance of Schooling: A Study of Changing Social Values in a Rural African Community"
    - RF 85067 A26 - Chege, Michael, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 283)
      Project title: "Coffee Production in Kenya: The Political Economy of an Export Commodity Staple"
    - RF 85067 A27 - Ohiorhenuan, John F. E., 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 284)
      Project title: "The Industrialization of Very Late Starters: Historical Experience, Prospects and Strategic Options for Nigeria"
    - RF 85067 A28 - Heng, Pek Koon, 1986-1988, 1991, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 285)
      Married name: Pek Koon Heng-Blackburn
      Project title: "Chinese Business Elites and Their Role in the Political Economy of Malaysia and Thailand"
    - RF 85067 A29 - Heryanto, Ariel, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 286)
      Project title: "Developing Words and Meanings in Indonesia's Development"
    - RF 85067 A30 - Bunbongkarn, Suchit, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 287)
      Project title: "The Military and the Politics of Rural Development in Thailand"
    - RF 85067 A31 - Mlama, Penina O., 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 288)
      Project title: "The Cultural Dimension of Development: The Case of Popular Theatre"
    - RF 85067 A32 - Hansen, Emmanuel, 1986-1989 (Box 48, Folder 289-290)
      Project title: "The African Crisis or Crisis in Africa: An Essay on Development Thinking, Development Experience and Development Practice"
    - RF 85067 A33 - Mojares, Resil B., 1986-1988, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 291)
      Project title: "Local Worlds: Moral Order and Social Change in Rural Philippines"
    - RF 85067 A34 - Cariño, Ledivina V., 1986-1988, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 292)
      Project title: "The Civil Service under Discontinuous Political Development"
    - RF 85067 A35 - Hutaserani, Suganya, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 293)
      Project title: "Migration and Urban Slums in Thailand: Reflections on Unequal Development"
    - RF 85067 A36 - Nindi, Benson Charles, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 294)
      Project title: "Political and Social Factors in Agricultural Policy: Tanzania"
    - RF 85070 - Bank Street College of Education - Computer Software for Inner-City Schools, 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 295-296)
    - RF 85078 A122 - Walter and Eliza Hall Institute of Medical Research - Leishmaniasis Immunization, 1985-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 49, Folder 297)
    - RF 85078 A123 - University of Oxford - Prenatal Diagnosis Programs for Thalassemia in Thailand, 1985-1989 (Box 50, Folder 298)
    - RF 85078 A124 - Case Western Reserve University - Protective Filarial Antigens, 1985-1989 (Box 50, Folder 299)
    - RF 85078 A125 - Brigham and Women's Hospital - Cellular Mechanisms of Immune Resistance in Experimental Cutaneous Leishmaniasis, 1986-1989 (Box 50, Folder 300)
    - RF 85078 A127 - Rockefeller University - Role of Trypanothione in Trypanosomatids, 1986, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 301)
    - RF 85078 A128 - Case Western Reserve University - Characterization of Schistosoma mansoni Protective Antigens, 1986-1989, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 302)
    - RF 85082 - Vivian Beaumont Theater, Inc. - Lincoln Center Theater, 1985-1991 (Box 50, Folder 303-306, Box 51, Folder 307-308)
    - RF 86003 A9 - Atlanta Partnership of Business & Education, Inc. - Humanities in the Secondary Schools, 1983-1989 (Box 51, Folder 309-312, Box 52, Folder 313-315)
    - RF 86003 A9 - Atlanta Partnership of Business & Education, Inc. - Humanities in the Secondary Schools: Supplementary Material (Box 52, Folder 316-317)
    - RF 86005 - Dance Works, Inc. - National Choreography Project, 1978-1979, 1981-1989 (Box 53, Folder 318-322, Box 54, Folder 323-326)
    - RF 86005 - Dance Works, Inc. - National Choreography Project: Supplementary Material (Box 54, Folder 327-328, Box 55, Folder 329-330)
    - RF 86006 - Single-Choreographer Dance Companies - New Works, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 331-333, Box 56, Folder 334)
      - Choreographers Meeting: Trisha Brown, Eliot Feld, Paul Taylor - Part 1, 1985 November 6; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 125 minutes (Tape AV 9995)
        Taped meeting at Rockefeller Foundation offices with choreographers Trisha Brown, Eliot Feld, and Paul Taylor. Brainstorming discussion about how to shape and develop a new RF choreographers program (Grant RF86006). Topics include: What should the grant criteria be?; Who should be funded?; What is the selection process?; Who should select?; Can a selector overcome personal bias?; Is selection subjective - or can it be objective?; How much should the funding amount be?; What is the grant trying to accomplish?; Where in the dance world is the need? Also, the choreographers discuss their methods of creation, as well as the difficulty of career continuity in dance. RF officers present (initials): ABA, HK, ESB, AAM.
        Access copy available.
      - Choreographers Meeting: Trisha Brown, Eliot Feld, Paul Taylor - Part 2, 1985 November 6; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 39 minutes (Tape AV 9996)
        Continuation of taped meeting at Rockefeller Foundation offices with Trisha Brown, Eliot Feld, and Paul Taylor. Topics include: Is there a crisis in ballet choreography (post-Balanchine)?; Discussion of the National Choreography Project, the Carlisle Project, and other dance residency programs.; Discussion of issues with matching grants.; The need for endowment development for dance companies.
    - RF 86006 A2 - Feld Ballet - New Dance Works, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 335)
    - RF 86006 A3 - Trisha Brown Company, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1986-1988 (Box 56, Folder 336)
    - RF 86006 A4 - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1987, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 337)
    - RF 86006 A5 - (The) House Foundation for the Arts, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 338)
    - RF 86006 A6 - Dean Dance and Music Foundation, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1987, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 339)
    - RF 86006 A7- Pick Up Performance Company, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 340)
    - RF 86006 A8 - Foundation for Independent Artists, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 341)
    - RF 86006 A9 - Contact Collaborations, Inc. - New Dance Works, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 342)
    - RF 86009 A3 - National Puerto Rican/Hispanic Voter Participation Project, Inc., 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 343)
    - RF 86009 A4 - League of Women Voters Education Fund - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring, 1984-1989 (Box 57, Folder 344-345)
    - RF 86011 A30 - Yoshida, Nobuko, 1985-1989 (Box 57, Folder 346)
    - RF 86011 A32 - Shaha, Chandrima, 1985-1990 (Box 57, Folder 347)
    - RF 86011 A33 - Chemtai, Alex K., 1985-1990 (Box 57, Folder 348)
    - RF 86011 A34 -Titanji, Vincent P. K., 1984-1990 (Box 58, Folder 349)
    - RF 86011 A35 - Ballejo, Gustavo, 1984-1991 (Box 58, Folder 350)
    - RF 86011 A36 - Hussain, Rabia, 1985-1990, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 351-352)
    - RF 86011 A38 - Saber, Mohamed Ali, 1985-1990 (Box 58, Folder 353)
    - RF 86011 A39 - Shaila, M. S., 1984-1989 (Box 58, Folder 354)
    - RF 86011 A40 - Grimaldi, Gabriel, Jr., 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 355-356)
    - RF 86011 A41- Orjih, Augustine U., 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 357)
    - RF 86011 A42 - Hossain, M. Anwar, 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 358)
    - RF 86011 A44 - Pua, Eng-Chong, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 359)
    - RF 86013 A63 - Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok - Diarrhea, 1986-1988 (Box 59, Folder 360)
      Project title: "The Incidence and Risk Factors of Diarrhea in Bangkok Low Socio-Economic Community"
    - RF 86013 A64 - Escola Paulista de Medicina, São Paulo - Cryptosporidiosis, 1986, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 361)
    - RF 86013 A65 - University of Newcastle, Australia - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1986, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 362)
      Project title: "Socio-Cultural Perspectives on Clinical Epidemiology Research"
    - RF 86013 A66 - Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1986-1987, 1989, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 363)
      Research grant for Dr. Leticia Legay Vermelho
    - RF 86013 A67 - Universidad de la Frontera, Chile - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 364)
      Research grant for Dr. Wilfreid Diener
    - RF 86013 A68 - Pontificia Universidad Javeriana, Bogotá - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1986, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 365)
      Research grant for Dr. Alvaro J. Ruiz
    - RF 86013 A69 - University of the Philippines - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 366)
      Research grant for Dr. Corazon Apolinar-Ngelangel
    - RF 86013 A70 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) - Clinical Epidemiology Training and Resource Center (CERTC) Advisory Committee Meetings, 1986, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 367)
    - RF 86013 A73 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) - Fifth Annual Meeting, 1986-1987, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 368-369)
    - RF 86013 A73 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) - Fifth Annual Meeting: Supplementary Material (Box 60, Folder 370-373, Box 61, Folder 374-376)
    - RF 86013 A78 - Instituto Nacional de la Nutrición, Mexico City - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1987, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 377)
      Research grant for Dr. Juan Calva
    - RF 86013 A79 - West China University of Medical Sciences - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1987, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 378)
      Research grant for Dr. Peng Hong Qi
    - RF 86013 A80 - Shanghai Medical University - Clinical Epidemiology Research, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 379)
      Research grant for Dr. Wang Ji Yao
    - RF 86014 A6 - Ministry of Public Health of China - Neurovirulence Testing Facility in China, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 380)
    - RF 86015 - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies, Singapore - Regional Strategic Studies Programme, 1980-1991 (Box 61, Folder 381-382, Box 62, Folder 383)
      Formerly 155
    - RF 86015 - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies, Singapore - Regional Strategic Studies Programme: Supplementary Material (Box 62, Folder 384-386, Box 63, Folder 387-391, Box 64, Folder 392-395)
    - RF 86016 - California Institute of Technology - Security and Foreign Policy Issues, 1985-1991 (Box 64, Folder 396-397, Box 65, Folder 398)
    - RF 86018 - Phelps-Stokes Fund - Bishop Desmond Tutu Southern African Refugee Scholarship Fund, 1985-1989, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 399-400)
    - RF 86023 - National Archives Trust Fund Board - Afro-American Editing Consortium, 1982-1989 (Box 65, Folder 401-403)
    - RF 86023 - National Archives Trust Fund Board - Afro-American Editing Consortium: Supplementary Material (Box 66, Folder 404-406)
    - RF 86033 - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Exhibition of Hispanic-American Art, 1982-1989 (Box 66, Folder 407, Box 67, Folder 408-411)
    - RF 86033 - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Exhibition of Hispanic-American Art: Supplementary Material (Box 67, Folder 412-413)
    - RF 86039 A119 - Allen, Richard L., 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 414)
      Study title: "Blacks, Black Media and Social Reality Effects"
    - RF 86039 A120 - Coleman, Lerita M., 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 415)
      Study title: "Evidence of Psychological Bondage: Toward a Better Understanding of Self-Stigmatization"
    - RF 86039 A121 - Harley, Sharon, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 416)
      Study title: "Myths Versus Reality: Gender, Work and Family Roles of Black Americans, 1917-1980"
    - RF 86039 A122 - Hurtado, Aida, 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 417)
      Study title: "Language Use and Language Attitudes of the Mexican Descent Population in the United States"
    - RF 86039 A123 - Zamora, Emilio, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 418)
      Study title: "Texas Mexican Labor Struggles, 1880-1940"
    - RF 86039 A124 - Arias, M. Beatriz, 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 419)
      Study title: "Multiracial Desegregation in California: 1970-1985"
    - RF 86039 A125 - McLoyd, Vonnie C., 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 420)
      Study title: Job Loss in Black Female-Headed Households: Response and Adaptation"
    - RF 86039 A126 - Walker, Juliet E. K., 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 421)
      Study title: "Black Entrepreneurship and Business Enterprise in Antebellum America"
    - RF 86039 A127 - Massey, Grace C., 1985-1989 (Box 68, Folder 422)
      Study title: "Continuities/Discontinuities: A Longitudinal Look at Black Students, Home and School"
    - RF 86039 A128 - Romero, Gloria J., 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 423)
      Study title: "Women Without Work: Stress and Coping Among Latinas and Blacks"
    - RF 86039 A129 - Mottl, Tahi L., 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 424)
      Study title: "Pathways to Success: Careers of Older Black and White Women"
    - RF 86039 A130 - Hero, Rodney E., 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 425)
      Study title: "Hispanic Political Representation-Incorporation and Governmental Responsiveness"
    - RF 86039 A132 - Upton, James N., 1987-1989 (Box 69, Folder 426)
      Study title: "The Impact of Financial Aid for Graduate Study for Black Students"
    - RF 86039 A134 - Jacobs, Sylvia M., 1987-1989, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 427)
      Study title: "A Call to Serve" Black American Missionaries in Africa"
    - RF 86039 A135 - Tsukashima, Ronald Tadao, 1987-1988, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 428)
      Study title: "An Ethnic Enterprise Among Japanese American Immigrants"
    - RF 86039 A136 - Martin, Waldo E., Jr., 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 429)
      Study title: "Cultural Politics and Black Consciousness: The 1960s"
    - RF 86039 A137 - Jackson, Byran O., 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 430)
      Study title: "Ethnic Group Consciousness and Political Behavior Among Black Americans" A Theoretical and Empirical Examination"
    - RF 86039 A138 - Jarrett, Robin L., 1987-1989 (Box 69, Folder 431)
      Study title" "Household Formation Patterns Among Low-Income Black Women"
    - RF 86039 A139 - Bradford, William D., 1987-1989 (Box 69, Folder 432)
      Study title: "Two Studies: Minority Household Wealth and Minority Commercial Banks"
    - RF 86039 A140 - Jones, Rhett S., 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 433)
      Study title: "Up South: Black Life in the Narragansett Country of Rhode Island, 1690-1790"
    - RF 86039 A142 - Winfield, Linda F., 1987-1989 (Box 70, Folder 434)
      Study title: "An Investigation of Characteristics of High vs. Low Literacy-Proficient Black Young Adults"
    - RF 86039 A143 - McBride, David, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 435)
      Study title: "From Tuberculosis to AIDS: Socio-Medical Reactions to Epidemics Among Urban Blacks, 1900-1986"
    - RF 86039 A144 - Robinson, Gwendolyn K., 1986-1989 (Box 70, Folder 436)
      Study title: "Ethnic Enterprise: A Sociopolitical History of the Afro-American Cosmetic Industry"
    - RF 86039 A145 - Mayfield, Lorraine P., 1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 437)
      Study title: "The Life Course of Adolescent Sexual Behavior"
    - RF 86039 A146 - Woodruff, Nancy D., 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 438)
      Study title: "Black Women Industrial Workers, 1890-1940: A Social History"
    - RF 86039 A147 - Dunson, Bruce H., 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 439)
      Study title: "The Black-White Unemployment Differential: The Effects of Changes in Industry and Occupational Employment"